=Spring Fever= =Episode 12=
=حمى الربيع= =الحلقة 12=
♪Willow buds by the shore, like soft rains of the past♪
♪ براعم الصفصاف على الشاطئ، مثل أمطار الماضي الناعمة♪
Swallow it.
ابتلعها.
Feeling any better?
هل تشعر بتحسن؟
Not yet.
ليس بعد.
This medicine is too strong.
هذا الدواء قوي جداً.
Are you still running a fever?
هل لا تزال تعاني من الحمى؟
Yes.
نعم.
What should we do?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل؟
Good work, guys.
عمل جيد يا شباب.
Come on. Drink.
تعال. اشرب.
- Drink up!
- اشرب!
Come on.
تعال.
Scar.
ندبة.
Out of wine! Get more!
نفذ النبيذ! احصل على المزيد!
Enjoy the food, boss.
استمتع بالطعام يا رئيس.
Wine's coming.
النبيذ قادم.
Hurry!
عجل!
How are you going to handle the Governor-General?
كيف ستتعامل مع الحاكم العام؟
It's troublesome.
إنه أمر مزعج.
How many men did we lose to him at the Goddess Temple?
كم من الرجال فقدناهم أمامه في معبد الإلهة؟
Let me kill him outright.
دعني أقتله على الفور.
Didn't the master say
ألم يقل المعلم؟
to wait for his word before we act?
أن ننتظر كلمته قبل أن نتصرف؟
If I can't touch him,
إذا لم أستطع لمسه،
can't I deal with that woman instead?
ألا يمكنني التعامل مع تلك المرأة بدلا من ذلك؟
Guys,
شباب،
watch how I take that woman down.
شاهد كيف أسقط تلك المرأة.
Come on!
تعال!
Guys, let's go there after the drink.
يا شباب، دعونا نذهب إلى هناك بعد الشراب.
- Okay!
-حسنا! -حسنا !
Scar.
ندبة.
Coming.
آت.
Hurry, Scar.
اسرع يا سكار.
I'm coming, boss.
أنا قادم يا رئيس.
Come on, boss.
هيا يا رئيس.
Fill it up.
املأها.
So you actually woke up?
فهل استيقظت فعلا؟
Impressive.
بديع.
But with the soft muscle powder,
ولكن مع مسحوق العضلات الناعمة،
you won't be moving anytime soon.
لن تتحرك في أي وقت قريب.
Soft muscle powder?
مسحوق العضلات الناعمة؟
- What are you doing? - Let her go. Take me instead!
- ماذا تفعل؟ - دعها تذهب. خذني أنا بدلاً منها!
Just watch how I will have fun
فقط شاهد كيف سأستمتع
with this beauty.
مع هذا الجمال.
Let me go.
دعني أذهب.
My beauty.
جمالي.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
- Let's have fun. - What are you doing?
- دعنا نستمتع. - ماذا تفعل؟
Let go of me.
أتركني.
Let go of me!
أتركني!
What's happening?
ماذا يحدث؟
There's really a mole.
هناك حقا شامة.
No wonder you weren't drugged.
لا عجب أنك لم تكن تحت تأثير المخدرات.
Turns out it has been swapped.
اتضح أنه تم تبديله.
Quiet. If you want to live, go with us.
هادئ. إذا كنت تريد أن تعيش، فاذهب معنا.
Drop the act, Lord Shen.
توقف عن هذا التصرف يا سيد شين.
You won't escape.
لن تهرب.
You weren't drugged?
لم يتم تخديرك؟
Let's go first.
دعنا نذهب أولا.
Go!
يذهب!
Stop!
قف!
Your hand's hurt.
يدك تؤلمك.
It's fine. But I'm truly poisoned now.
لا بأس، لكنني مسمومٌ حقًا الآن.
Let's go first.
دعنا نذهب أولا.
Go.
يذهب.
Search! Hurry!
ابحث! اسرع!
Check thoroughly.
تأكد جيدا.
♪Pearl curtains lift, pipa notes resound♪
♪ترتفع ستائر اللؤلؤ، وتتردد نغمات البيبا♪
♪Subtle brows traced, golden blooms adorned♪
♪حواجب دقيقة مرسومة، وأزهار ذهبية مزينة♪
♪A song concludes, earning mere silver coins♪
♪تنتهي الأغنية بكسب مجرد عملات فضية♪
♪With one dance, I'll awe the world♪
♪ برقصة واحدة، سأبهر العالم ♪
Check here.
انقر هنا.
Keep eyes sharp!
حافظ على عينيك حادة!
♪Late at night, I see you study by the window♪
♪في وقت متأخر من الليل، أراك تدرس بجانب النافذة♪
♪In humble hemp robes, our gazes meet with longing♪
♪في أردية القنب المتواضعة، تلتقي نظراتنا بالشوق♪
♪Your scholarly grace shines undeniable♪
♪نعمتك العلمية تتألق بشكل لا يمكن إنكاره♪
♪Years pass, yet you remain absent♪
♪تمر السنوات، ولكنك تظل غائبًا♪
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
♪Half a life of passion yields in pages of folly♪
♪نصف حياة من العاطفة تنتج في صفحات من الحماقة♪
♪How could I ever match a scholar of your rank♪
♪كيف يمكنني أن أضاهي عالمًا من رتبتك♪
I don't understand.
لا أفهم.
Didn't you say I am your bait?
ألم تقل أنني طُعمك؟
Why didn't you use me?
لماذا لم تستخدميني؟
I investigated alone.
لقد قمت بالتحقيق بمفردي.
I didn't want to drag you in.
لم أكن أريد أن أجرك.
Why?
لماذا؟
You still don't understand?
هل مازلت لا تفهم؟
♪Years pass, yet you remain absent♪
♪تمر السنوات، ولكنك تظل غائبًا♪
They won't find us quickly.
لن يجدونا بسرعة.
You should take a rest.
ينبغي عليك أن تأخذ قسطاً من الراحة.
Fine.
بخير.
♪How could I ever match a scholar of your rank♪
♪كيف يمكنني أن أضاهي عالمًا من رتبتك♪
♪Years pass, yet you remain absent♪
♪تمر السنوات، ولكنك تظل غائبًا♪
♪A lone goose bears a letter of two poetic lines♪
♪أوزة وحيدة تحمل رسالة من سطرين شعريين♪
♪Half a life of passion yields in pages of folly♪
♪نصف حياة من العاطفة تنتج في صفحات من الحماقة♪
♪How could I ever match a scholar of your rank♪
♪كيف يمكنني أن أضاهي عالمًا من رتبتك♪
(Running so long in the summer heat,)
(الجري لفترة طويلة في حرارة الصيف)
(I'm drenched in sweat.)
(أنا غارق في العرق.)
(Who knows if I stink already.)
(من يدري إن كنت كريه الرائحة بالفعل.)
My lord?
سيدي؟
(It looks like)
(يبدو مثل)
(the poison knocked him out.)
(السم جعله يفقد الوعي.)
♪Grind flesh between grit and stone♪
♪طحن اللحم بين الحصى والحجر♪
♪Sink into pain, only then are pearls born♪
♪الغرق في الألم، حينها فقط تولد اللآلئ♪
♪Wait until abyssal darkness stains every inch of skin♪
♪انتظر حتى يلطخ الظلام السحيق كل شبر من الجلد♪
♪Then comes the time to chase the dawn♪
♪ثم يأتي الوقت لمطاردة الفجر♪
A'man.
أمان.
♪Passing wind♪
♪ريح عابرة♪
♪Entwine my hair in dance♪
♪تشابك شعري في الرقص♪
♪I'll lean into his embrace♪
♪سأستند إلى حضنه♪
♪Wade through deep seas♪
♪خوض البحار العميقة♪
♪Bathing in affection♪
♪الاستحمام في المودة♪
♪Condensing into rain♪
♪تكثف إلى مطر♪
♪Who cast a frantic, lingering glance♪
♪الذي ألقى نظرة محمومة ومتباطئة♪
What am I thinking? She's just freshening up.
ماذا أفكر؟ إنها فقط تنعش نفسها.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
Could she be
هل يمكن أن تكون
accepting my feelings?
قبول مشاعري؟
Or am I dreaming?
أم أنني أحلم؟
Yes. You're dreaming.
نعم انت تحلم
It scared me. It's really just a dream.
لقد أخافني. إنه مجرد حلم.
No, it can't be.
لا، لا يمكن أن يكون.
It can't be.
لا يمكن أن يكون.
Stop there!
توقف هنا!
Stop!
قف!
Stop! Stop!
توقف! توقف!
Don't run!
لا تركض!
After her!
بعدها!
Stop!
قف!
You shameless woman.
يا لك من امرأة وقحة.
Such a persistent runner.
مثل هذا العداء المثابر.
Take her down!
خذها إلى الأسفل!
Chai Er?
تشاي إير؟
Scar,
ندبة،
after hiding for years,
بعد الاختباء لسنوات،
you've finally shown yourself.
لقد أظهرت نفسك أخيرا.
Neither of you escapes today.
لا أحد منكم ينجو اليوم.
I'll tell you where the accusation letter is.
سأخبرك أين رسالة الإتهام.
Let her go.
اسمح لها أن تذهب.
Keep dreaming.
استمر بالحلم.
It's in the textile shop at the Baiyi Alley.
إنه في متجر النسيج في زقاق بايي.
I'll hold them off.
سأمنعهم.
You go first.
أنت تذهب أولا.
Escape via the waterway behind.
الهروب عبر الممر المائي خلف.
Hold your breath.
احبس أنفاسك.
Float like a lotus leaf.
تطفو مثل ورقة اللوتس.
Drift with the current and you'll be safe.
انجرف مع التيار وستكون آمنًا.
Sister, when swimming, float like a lotus leaf.
أختي، عندما تسبحين، تطفين مثل ورقة اللوتس.
If you can float, you'll be safe.
إذا كنت تستطيع أن تطفو، فسوف تكون آمنًا.
I just want you to keep playing with me like this.
أريدك فقط أن تستمر في اللعب معي بهذه الطريقة.
You're my brother?
أنت أخي؟
You're alive?
هل انت على قيد الحياة؟
Kill him!
اقتله!
Stop!
قف!
Nobody moves! Stay put!
لا أحد يتحرك! ابق في مكانك!
Shen Que.
شين كيو.
Take her away.
خذها بعيدا.
You can't die yet.
لا يمكنك أن تموت بعد .
Leave this to me.
اترك هذا لي.
Go!
يذهب!
Move.
يتحرك.
Shen Que!
شين كيو!
Go!
يذهب!
It's fine.
إنه بخير.
I'm okay.
انا بخير.
You've been hiding here all these years?
لقد كنت مختبئًا هنا كل هذه السنوات؟
I was scared as a child.
لقد كنت خائفة عندما كنت طفلة.
So I drifted outside for years.
لذلك انجرفت خارجًا لسنوات.
Later, I was caught by bandits and forced into labor,
وفي وقت لاحق، تم القبض علي من قبل قطاع الطرق وأجبروني على العمل،
which ironically kept me safe.
وهو ما ساعدني بشكل مثير للسخرية على البقاء آمنًا.
I slept peacefully too.
لقد نمت بسلام أيضاً.
You'd already escaped the woods.
لقد هربت بالفعل من الغابة.
Why did you come back?
لماذا عدت؟
- Why did you... - Back then...
- لماذا فعلت... - في ذلك الوقت...
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
Princess Anhe's handwritten accusation letter
رسالة اتهام مكتوبة بخط اليد للأميرة آنه
was in the bundle you gave me.
كان في الحزمة التي أعطيتني إياها.
Only by letting them know I'm alive,
فقط من خلال إعلامهم بأنني على قيد الحياة،
can you stay safe.
هل يمكنك البقاء آمنًا؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I should've been the one taking care of you.
كان ينبغي أن أكون الشخص الذي يعتني بك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Sister,
أخت،
we shouldn't wait long for Lord Shen here.
لا ينبغي لنا أن ننتظر اللورد شين هنا لفترة طويلة.
Taodu's crawling with pirates.
تاودو يزحف مع القراصنة.
We must find another place soon.
يجب علينا أن نجد مكانا آخر قريبا.
Attack!
هجوم!
After them!
بعدهم!
This way.
من هنا.
Where'd they go? After them!
أين ذهبوا؟ بعدهم!
Sis, no time for details.
أختي، ليس لدي وقت للتفاصيل.
Just listen.
فقط استمع .
Once past this door, pirates thin out.
بمجرد عبور هذا الباب، يتضاءل عدد القراصنة.
The accusation letter is in the textile shop at Baiyi Alley.
توجد رسالة الإتهام في محل النسيج في شارع بايي.
Deliver it personally to the Young Lord of Duke Xuan's Mansion.
قم بتسليمه شخصيًا إلى اللورد الشاب لقصر دوق شوان.
Mu, we'll survive together
مو، سوف ننجو معًا
and clear the Sang family's name.
وتبرئة اسم عائلة سانغ.
There's no time.
ليس هناك وقت.
There they are! After them!
ها هم! بعدهم!
Go! Hurry!
إذهب! بسرعة!
Mu!
في!
Go!
يذهب!
Mu, let's go together.
مو، دعنا نذهب معًا.
Mu, what're you doing?
مو ماذا تفعل؟
Mu!
في!
Mu, open the door!
مو افتح الباب!
Why?
لماذا؟
They killed Princess Anhe.
لقد قتلوا الأميرة أنهي.
The Lu family and Prefect Xia are in cahoots,
عائلة لو والحاكم شيا متواطئان،
deceiving the people of Ningzhou.
خداع شعب نينغتشو.
You must live.
يجب عليك أن تعيش.
Open up! Listen to me!
افتح! استمع لي!
Open the door!
افتح الباب!
For Jin!
لجين!
For our parents!
لوالدينا!
Mu!
في!
For all of Ningzhou!
لجميع نينغتشو!
Open the door!
افتح الباب!
Mu!
في!
Mu, open the door!
مو افتح الباب!
Go, Sister!
إذهبي يا أختي!
We must live together.
يجب علينا أن نعيش معاً.
Go!
يذهب!
Sometimes living requires more courage than dying.
في بعض الأحيان تتطلب الحياة شجاعة أكبر من الموت.
- Mu! - Go!
- مو! - اذهب!
No hesitation. No cowardice. Go!
لا تردد. لا جبن. انطلق!
- No! Open the door! - Don't make me look down on you.
- لا! افتح الباب! - لا تجعلني أنظر إليك باستخفاف.
Mu!
في!
My cover is blown.
لقد تم الكشف عن غطائي.
You must avenge what remains of our grievances.
يجب عليك الانتقام لما تبقى من مظالمنا.
Mu.
في.
Open the door.
افتح الباب.
(If I die, only you know where the evidence is.)
(إذا متُّ، فأنت وحدك من يعرف مكان الدليل.)
(So you can survive.)
(لكي تتمكن من البقاء على قيد الحياة.)
I'm begging you, Mu.
أنا أتوسل إليك يا مو.
Open the door.
افتح الباب.
♪Grind flesh between grit and stone♪
♪طحن اللحم بين الحصى والحجر♪
♪Sink into pain, only then are pearls born♪
♪الغرق في الألم، حينها فقط تولد اللآلئ♪
♪Wait until abyssal darkness stains every inch of skin♪
♪انتظر حتى يلطخ الظلام السحيق كل شبر من الجلد♪
♪Then comes the time to chase the dawn♪
♪ثم يأتي الوقت لمطاردة الفجر♪
♪I'll sweep through dusty sands♪
♪سأمسح الرمال المتربة♪
♪Passing wind♪
♪ريح عابرة♪
♪Entwine my hair in dance♪
♪تشابك شعري في الرقص♪
♪I'll lean into his embrace♪
♪سأستند إلى حضنه♪
♪Wade through deep seas♪
♪خوض البحار العميقة♪
♪Bathing in affection♪
♪الاستحمام في المودة♪
♪Condensing into rain♪
♪تكثف إلى مطر♪
♪Who cast a frantic, lingering glance♪
♪الذي ألقى نظرة محمومة ومتباطئة♪
♪Carrying endless tenderness♪
♪تحمل حنانًا لا نهاية له♪
♪Gazing through eons of moonlit winds♪
♪التحديق عبر عصور من الرياح المضاءة بالقمر♪
♪Turn tears to pearls and cradle them within♪
♪حوّل الدموع إلى لآلئ واحتضنها في داخلك♪
♪Henceforth we walk the mortal realm♪
♪من الآن فصاعدا نسير في عالم البشر♪
♪Across vast mountains and rivers♪
♪عبر الجبال والأنهار الشاسعة♪
♪I'll sweep through dusty sands♪
♪سأمسح الرمال المتربة♪
♪Passing wind♪
♪ريح عابرة♪
♪Entwine my hair in dance♪
♪تشابك شعري في الرقص♪
♪I'll lean into his embrace♪
♪سأستند إلى حضنه♪
♪Wade through deep seas♪
♪خوض البحار العميقة♪
♪Bathing in affection♪
♪الاستحمام في المودة♪
♪Condensing into rain♪
♪تكثف إلى مطر♪